Burton, John, Papers /4121
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John Burton Papers
1974-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Burton, John
/4121
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
7994466
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4053m: ILR School Report on the Off-Campus Labor Relations Credit Programs /4250: Ronald Seeber and Robert S. Smith New York State Workers Compensation Pilot Program for Alternative Dispute Resolution Files 6047: Archives Information File
Burton, John
7994466
- ALABAMA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ALASKA: Law, etc. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ARIZONA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ARKANSAS: Law (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ALASKA: Correspondence, Misc. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alberta - Canada (Box 1, Folder 6)
- British Columbia, Vancouver - Canada (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CALIFORNIA: Law, Reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CALIFORNIA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CALIFORNIA: Correspondence, Interviews, etc. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CALIFORNIA MIS, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Scope and Contents
  November 1974
- CALIFORNIA (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CALIFORNIA, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CALIFORNIA - PPD (Box 1, Folder 14)
- CALIFORNIA Safety, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- COLORADO: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CONNECTICUT: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- DELAWARE: Forms (Box 2, Folder 2)
- DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA: Law (Box 2, Folder 3)
- FLORIDA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- FLORIDA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- GEORGIA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- HAWAII: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- HAWAII: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- IDAHO: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- IDAHO: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ILLINOIS: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILLINOIS: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ILLINOIS: Publications of Compensable Work Injuries (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ILLINOIS: W.C. Field Trip Info (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ILLINOIS: Industrial Commission (Box 2, Folder 15)
- INDIANA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- IOWA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- KANSAS: Correspondence, Notes, etc. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- KENTUCKY: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- KENTUCKY: Correspondence, etc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- LOUISIANA: Law (Box 2, Folder 21)
- MAINE: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 22)
- MARYLAND: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 23)
- MARYLAND: Correspondence, Notes, etc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- MASSACHUSETTS: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- MICHIGAN: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- MICHIGAN: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- MICHIGAN: Correspondence., Interview, Notes, etc. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- MICHIGAN: W.C. Field Trip (Box 3, Folder 6)
- MINNESOTA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- MINNESOTA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- MISSISSIPPI: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- MISSISSIPPI: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- MISSOURI: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- MONTANA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- MONTANA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- MONTANA: Correspondence., Interview, Notes, etc. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- NEBRASKA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- NEVADA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- NEVADA: Industrial Commission (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NEVADA - PPD (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NEVADA (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Newfoundland and Labrador (Box 4, Folder 6)
- New Brunswick - Canada (Box 4, Folder 7)
- NEW HAMPSHIRE: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- NEW HAMPSHIRE: Correspondence., Notes, etc. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- NEW JERSEY: Annual Reports (Box 4, Folder 10)
- NEW JERSEY: Division of Research and Planning WC First Reports and OSHA (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Own Notes on NEW JERSEY W.C. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- NEW JERSEY (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NEW JERSEY (Box 5, Folder 2)
- NEW JERSEY: Forms and Coding Sheets, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- NEW JERSEY: WC Bureau of Engineering and Safety (Box 5, Folder 4)
- NEW JERSEY: WC Agency Forms etc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- NEW JERSEY: Correspondence., Notes, etc. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- NEW MEXICO: Law, etc. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NEW YORK: Law, etc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NEW YORK: Publications (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NEW YORK: W.C. Operations Division (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NEW YORK: W.C., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  March 17, 1975
- NEW YORK: Publications (Box 6, Folder 2)
- N. CAROLINA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- N. CAROLINA: Correspondence., Notes, etc. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- N. DAKOTA: Law, etc. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Nova Scotia (Box 6, Folder 6)
- OHIO: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- OKLAHOMA: Correspondence., Interview, Forms (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Ontario W.C. Main File (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Ontario Supplementary File (Box 6, Folder 10)
- OREGON: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- OREGON: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- OREGON (Box 7, Folder 1)
- PENNSYLVANIA (Box 7, Folder 2)
- PENNSYLVANIA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- PENNSYLVANIA: Law and Forms, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  January 1975
- PENNSYLVANIA: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- PENNSYLVANIA (Box 7, Folder 6)
- PENNSYLVANIA: Correspondence., etc. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Prince Edward Island (Box 7, Folder 8)
- PUERTO RICO: Law, etc. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- PUERTO RICO: Correspondence., etc. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Quebec (Box 7, Folder 11)
- RHODE ISLAND: Law, etc. (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Saskatchewan (Box 7, Folder 13)
- S. CAROLINA: Correspondence., etc. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- S. CAROLINA: Law (Box 7, Folder 15)
- S. CAROLINA: Forms (Box 7, Folder 16)
- S. DAKOTA: Correspondence., etc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- S. DAKOTA: Law (Box 8, Folder 2)
- TENNESSEE: Law (Box 8, Folder 3)
- TENNESSEE: Correspondence., etc. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- TEXAS: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Labor: Correspondence. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- UTAH: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- VERMONT: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- VIRGINIA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- WASHINGTON: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- WASHINGTON: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- WEST VIRGINIA: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 12)
- WISCONSIN: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- WISCONSIN: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- WYOMING: Law, Annual Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
- WYOMING: Forms, Statistical Reports, etc. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Workmen's Compensation Tables (Box 8, Folder 17)